fumikomu ze akuseru
press down hard on the gas
kakehiki wa nai sa sou dayo
that's right, there's no compromise
yoru wo nukeru
we'll slip through the night
nejikomu sa saigo ni
at the final moment push hard
sashihiki zero sa sou dayo
that's right, all the way to zero
hibi wo kezuru
until we wipe away the days
kokoro wo sotto
gently open your heart
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
if you pull it close to you
todoku yo kitto
it will reach you, without a doubt
tsutau yo motto sa aa
it will come, closer, now
iki isoide shiboritotte
we're speeding through life, squeezing it for all of its worth
motsureru ashi
our feet are tied
dakedo mae yori zutto sou tooku he
but we still keep going further
ubaitotte tsukandatte
even if I take it back, and grasp it
kimi janai nara
if you're not the one
imi wa nai no sa
there will be no meaning
dakara haruka kanata
and so we'll go far off into the distance
Umm, where's the room
that Sasuke's in?
Sasuke-sama is not allowed
any visitors.
What?! Hey, hey!
What's up with that?!
I'm sorry,
those are the rules.
Why, nee-chan, tell me why?
Naruto, this is a hospital.
Keep it down.
Hey! Hey!
I've got a favor to ask!
You don't need to say it all.
Well, I thought it would
come to this so...
I searched for someone
to watch your training.
Why?!
I want you to, Kakashi-sensei!
I have some matters
to take care of.
I don't have time to
trouble myself with you.
Oh! Aha...!
You're going to
train Sasuke, aren't you?!
Well... don't say that.
I found a sensei who's
more reliable than I am!
Well... who is it?
It's me!
Huh?!
Oh!
You!
The Closet Perv!
Such insolence!
Ebisu Returns!
I Will Not Allow
Shamelessness!
Ebisu-sensei is
a Closet Perv?
Why's this guy
my training teacher?!
In the first place,
he's weaker than me!
What did you say?
But you see! But you see!
A long time ago,
with my Harem Jutsu, this guy...
Transform!
Ebisu-sama! Ebisu-sama!
B-By any chance...
Harem Jutsu?
U-Uh... it's nothing!
I'll treat you to and buy you
whatever you want later!
Just be quiet about that!
You better.
Wow, I didn't know you
were acquainted.
Well, they're unsavory ties, but.
How could I ever forget
that humiliation?
But why this guy?
I definitely don't want him to.
Same here.
If it weren't Kakashi-kun's favor,
who'd teach you for the fun of it?
Then don't.
Now now, both of you...
Don't say that.
Naruto, Ebisu-sensei is a private tutor
who teaches the elite,
a special Jonin!
He's truly better
at teaching than I am.
Well, Naruto, of the three kids
in Team 7 that I taught,
you're the worst at the basic skills.
Get taught with care
this time around.
How the hell am I inferior
compared to Sakura-chan and Sasuke?!
Naruto, it's fact that you
don't have the fundamentals down.
No matter what you do,
the basic skills are important.
If you really want to become strong,
just be quiet and listen to what I say.
Now then, Ebisu-sensei,
I'm leaving him with you.
Yes, yes.
Damn it.
It may appear to be harsh,
but you can become a lot more stronger.
Do your best.
Okay, then, let's go.
Still, I'm not convinced...
Huh?
You see!
Fundamentals might be important,
but I won't get strong being taught
by someone weaker than me!
So in other words,
you want to say that I'm weak?
Who else is here?!
I was certainly surprised having
that indecent Jutsu used on me that time.
But it's premature for you to
judge my ability on just that.
Even though you were
totally knocked out.
Fine.
Then, why don't we put
it to the test?
Hmm?
Naruto-kun, run.
Huh?
If you can outrun me,
I'll back down quietly.
Back down...?
Yes.
And of course, I'll speak to
Kakashi-sensei
about you receiving direct training.
What?! Really?!
This elite instructor does not
go back on his word.
However, this is only if
you can outrun me.
Then that makes it easy!
See ya!
This'll be a snap, a snap!
I'll lose that...
Closet Perv in no time!
He already can't catch up!
I knew I was quite
an exceptional Ninja...
Who is exceptional, you say?
Surely you're not thinking you can
outrun me with just that much.
W-What're you saying?!
The chase has still...
only just begun!
Though he's a Closet Perv,
he's the elite tutor after all,
he's good.
Now then.
I knew you were a Closet Perv.
What are you doing...?
Naruto-kun?
I see. The idea isn't bad.
Then, how about this?!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Heh!
Catch me... if you can!
Not bad...
However, you are not the only one
who uses the Shadow Clone Jutsu.
I won't let you get away!
Damn it!
Son... of... a...!
Now then, next.
Hold it!
I found you!
Wait!
I won't let you
get away!
Get off!
There!
No, actually, here!
Here!
There!
Hold it!
Have you reached your limit?
You're freaking pesky!
Give it up already!
What are you snapping
back at me for?
This is a chase, so chasing
is natural, right?
T-True enough...
Naruto-kun, you have understood
my greatness by now, right?
It's about time you surrendered
and moved on to training...
The hell with that!
I'm going to bump you off,
and receive Kakashi-sensei's training!
Even if I have to knock you out!
It appears you still have
some spirit left.
To think he would come at me
head on, even though this is a chase.
Just what I would expect of you, Naruto-kun.
As Kakashi-kun said, he's the
most unpredictable Ninja.
Don't take this badly!
Eat this!
Clone Jutsu...?
The game is over, Naruto-kun!
Damn it!
Miso-flavor barbecued pork noodles and
salt-flavor ramen noodles!
Here you go!
Naruto-kun, having been shown
your movements and
having further analyzed
what Kakashi-sensei has told me...
it is clear that you cannot control
Chakra well.
Control...?
That's right.
Now then, comparing you
with Sasuke-kun and Sakura-kun...
I shall explain your
bad points in order.
As you know, in the case of using
Ninjutsu, Genjutsu and the like,
Ninja build up Chakra and
activate the Jutsu.
I-I know that already!
Is that so?
Then, in the case of comparing
the three of you,
I shall explain specifically
how you are inferior.
That's kind of an irritating
way of saying it.
I'm treating you the ramen
as promised,
so be quiet and listen!
First, let us say that Sakura
uses Clone Jutsu.
Clone Jutsu!
In her case, her build-up control as well as
her control of Chakra is perfect,
so she can make clones without
using wasteful energy.
Shannaro!
Next, in Sasuke-kun's case,
he is somewhat poor at
building up Chakra.
Clone Jutsu.
But, his control of Chakra is perfect,
so both he and Sakura-kun can
make five clones.
But, he uses a bit more wasteful
Chakra than Sakura-kun.
Oh!
So Sasuke's nothing special.
In your case, there's no time
to be laughing at others.
Huh?
You are very poor at building up Chakra
and controlling it,
so you cannot make clones
with the same amount of Chakra.
In the case where you strain to
make clones despite that,
after consuming a much larger amount
of Chakra than Sakura-kun and Sasuke-kun...
Clone Jutsu!
...you can barely make
one clone at best.
By the way,
Sakura-kun and Sasuke-kun can become ten
with the same amount of Chakra.
Like this, the three of you are
this different even using the same Jutsu.
Well, this is a somewhat exaggerated
comparison of you three,
but you build up too much Chakra,
use too much physical strength,
and your Jutsu activation is also unstable.
But, there've been times when
I was greater than Sakura-chan and Sasuke...
That's only because you
happen to have
the most outstanding stamina
of the three!
Well, I am pretty sure that
your Chakra control
is getting difficult due to the influence
of the Nine-Tails...
which is the origin of your stamina.
Anyway, there is no mistaking
that you can become strong
if you carry out the training
we will be doing from now.
Huh?! Really?!
I guarantee it.
Now then, let's go.
Sir, your bill.
Oh, that's right.
Wha...?!
Thank you very much!
We've come quite a long way...
But, this is a hot spring town, right?
It doesn't look like we've come
here to leisurely soak in a hot spring...
Hey! Naruto-kun!
That's the women's bath!
I simply will not allow
indecent behavior!
Huh?
I'm not you...
It's not that I was trying to peep.
Thinking of something like that
in the first place makes you a Closet Perv!
What's with that look?
N-Nothing.
More importantly, why've we come
to a place like this?!
Will soaking in a hot spring
do anything for training?
No!
The training will be here
in this hot spring area!
Okay, this is the place.
It's a bath, sure enough!
What are you saying?
I said this is training, didn't I?
Training!
We're going to train here?
What the hell are we going to do?
Walk on this hot water!
What?!
What is it?
Walk on hot water?
Can you really do that?
Of course!
I heard from Kakashi-sensei.
You already did tree-climbing training
without using your hands, right?
It's an application of that.
Hmm...
What do you mean?
Besides, I don't really remember
stuff from long ago!
In tree climbing, all you do
is accumulate
only the necessary amount of Chakra
in one necessary location
and maintain that amount of
Chakra all the while.
Trees are fixed objects,
so you only need to be attached to it.
In other words,
it's training for building up
a fixed amount of Chakra.
To float on the surface of water,
you have to discharge on
a constant basis
an appropriate amount of Chakra
from your feet to the water
and balance that to the extent that
you can float your own body.
Huh?
This Chakra control is
more difficult than maintaining...
and is a control training for
discharge and usage of fixed amount
of Chakra for Jutsu and alike.
Hmm, I really don't get it!
Well, it would be better to
show you in your case.
First, you build up Chakra
in your feet.
Then, while constantly discharging
a fixed amount...
you balance it with your body weight.
And...
well, this is how it goes.
Oh! Okay!
I'm going to try!
First, you build up Chakra
in your feet.
Then!
Discharge a fixed amount. Right?
Oh!
I knew it.
Hot, hot, hot, hot!
I forgot to mention it,
but this hot water is 60°C.
If you do nothing but fail...
you will become a boiled octopus!
Damn it!
I'll do it no matter what!
You're unusually spirited today,
honored grandson!
My principle of guidance
has finally gotten through!
This would ordinarily be the
time to go carry out
a surprise attack on Hokage-sama.
I've stopped doing that now!
That's right!
So you have finally understood.
That the shortcut to becoming
the Hokage is to do as I say...
There are no shortcuts!
Huh?
Naruto nii-chan said it...
If you're to become Hokage,
be prepared for that!
Oh!
I'm starting to get it!
To think he would get the
hang of the Chakra control this quickly...
I never thought,
you would grow this much.
Indeed, there are no shortcuts,
in anything...
It appears I had the
wrong idea about you...
You are a much smarter teacher
than I am.
And, you were not just a Demon Fox...
You were a splendid
Hidden Leaf Village Ninja!
Oh! Hot!
Hm?! That is...!
Humph! I don't know who you are
or where you're from, but...
I will not allow indecency!
Man...
T-That is!
What?!
Don't make a ruckus.
Jeez, it won't do to be found out!
The Closet Perv lost?
W-What's with that
Shameless Perv?!
ONE JAMPU ichiban SURAMU DANKU kamasu TAISON
One! first, Tyson jumps and slam-dunks
TWO are mo kore mo dosoku de HAGU KISSU I LOVE YOU
Owo! he kisses and hugs everyone randomly and says "I love you"
THREE YOGA wo kiwamemasu KAREE kirai masara san
Three! Masala masters yoga but hates curry
FOUR hetare tougyuushi SANCHESU OREI
Four! Sanchez is a lousy bullfighter, olay!
sekaijuu hora waratteru sora miagete saa tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
ONE kokuen bori ni bottou bodi ma haattaya san mo
One! Bodimahattaya devotes his time for digging black ships
TWO PEKIN DAKKU waiyaa AKUSHON chari de isogu CHEN RII
Two! peking Duck, action scene, Chen Lee speeds around on his bike
THREE MY KOTEKA daiji ni migakiageru POPO san
Three! Popo loves to polish his coteka
FOUR ote wo haishaku JAPANIIZU PIIPOO
Four! japanese people, now lend me your hand!
sekaijuu hora waratteru sora miagete saa tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
sekaijuu hora kawatteku minna ganbatte so tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, you!
What're you doing,
Shameless Perv?!
Here I was having my training watched,
and you did this to the Closet Perv!
And you're so infernally
quick at running away.
Could he be a super Ninja?
Next episode.
"Coming Soon! Enter the Perverted Hermit!"
I'll chase him down and make him
train me without fail!